[{"answer": "I would be very cautious about saying that, Piers, unless I had some kind of substantiation to it.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Is there any merit to the argument that these numbers aren't quite what they seem?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "I think the debate certainly does.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 60, "question": "Do you think that either of these things, in the last 24 hours, Barack Obama's very lackluster, surprisingly poor debate performance, or these job numbers today, do either of them constitute in any form a kind of game change moment?", "qSentId": 59}, {"answer": "I think so, Piers, but you know, it would sound like I am now trying to rewrite history or I would have done better.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "Do you think you would have done better against the Obama that was debating this week?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "I don't know but I hope he repeats this latest one, where the middle class America has been buried for the last four years.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Are you hoping that he's going to be giving some sprinkling of presents back to you guys?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "Well, let me tell you what's not vague, and that is five days after, five days after what was very quickly determined by the intelligence committee as a terrorist attack, they trotted out our ambassador to the U.N. to every major news outlet saying that this was a spontaneous demonstration because of a hateful video.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "What is your assessment of where we are now?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "Are you in favor of that?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "I have no information on that.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 119, "question": "Do you have any information on that?", "qSentId": 118}, {"answer": "Actually, I love and cherish Big Bird.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 126, "question": "Would you or would you not kill Big Bird?", "qSentId": 125}, {"answer": "I mean, it's a paradox.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 156, "question": "What went wrong?", "qSentId": 155}, {"answer": "I mean, it's certainly closer but there's always going to be good news and bad news.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "I mean, would you anticipate a tightening of the polls and a very, very close race now?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "Well, he's certainly right on that.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "I just took a call from Big Bird before coming on here.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 218, "question": "How do you feel about the fact Mitt Romney if he gets into power will get rid of you?", "qSentId": 217}, {"answer": "Not in my -- obviously I'm a little conflicted here because my show was just on PBS.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Does he have a point, Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I guess I would argue that they are as good as either you're saying or particularly that Obama is saying.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 250, "question": "How much has that been dissipated by what are undeniably very good jobs figures today?", "qSentId": 249}, {"answer": "Well, I think the timing was right that he said that, but I do hope he doesn't move away from what the bigger argument that he was trying to make, is that there are two choices in America today.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "Was that a smart political move in a moment of everyone feeling good about you to just bury that away?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "He does.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 296, "question": "The man has a record of constantly flip-flopping on issues, doesn't he?", "qSentId": 295}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I do think the start of the presidential campaign, in some ways, started with the debate the other night.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What do you say to Mitt Romney?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Oh, absolutely.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Can he win from here, do you think, John?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "That's -- yes, that's right.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 371, "question": "Is it four million people now watch your video lessons, for want of a better phrase, right?", "qSentId": 370}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "And you've taken that kind of philosophy and said, right, we're going to make these like a short, sharp shock, right?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "I -- I think there's going to be a broad push to making classrooms more human.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 403, "question": "With other countries now steaming past America, what is the number one thing you want to see, whoever wins the next election, do about this?", "qSentId": 402}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 412, "question": "But is the -- is the -- the right move forward for kids to be doing as much work at home as they do at school and doing it on computers, which is their natural habitat anyway?", "qSentId": 411}, {"answer": "-- you know, I have to tell you, he -- he has always been so nice to me.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "-- just casually referencing you like that?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "Well, yes, you can say that.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "It's amazing, because -- I mean, do I assume that your politics lean the Republican way?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "I thought it went really well.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "So after the debate, you must have been a happy guy this week, yes?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I haven't done that, but I'll tell you what I have done.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Have you ever walked into a karaoke bar and sung one of your own songs without people knowing it's you?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "I mean no man can do something finer for another man than that, can he?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "-- his own songs.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Lionel?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Have you ever made love to a woman to your own music?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Maybe.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "Would you tell me if you had?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "We've been married 15 years.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "Twenty years?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "Well, at least five.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "How many times would you say you've been properly in love in your life?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "That might be a record, I think.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 569, "question": "-- wouldn't you say?", "qSentId": 568}, {"answer": "I -- yes, I -- I think I'm codependent.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 575, "question": "You're an incurable romantic, really, aren't you, Kenny?", "qSentId": 574}, {"answer": "Who -- it would probably be \"Lady,\" because I think it -- well, in all fairness, the song I enjoy singing more now, maybe because I haven't done it as much, I'd do \"We've Got Tonight\" in the show, a song I did with Sheena.", "docId": "121005pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Final question, if you could be trapped on a desert island and you could only sing one of your songs again for the rest of your life, what would it be?", "qSentId": 580}]